<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ReaderDetails updated="08/06/2026 10:48:08">
  <Reader>
    <Name>Barb</Name>
    <Description>I am a natural intuitive empath and highly sensitive to the feelings of others. I consider myself to be  A Light Worker . I will tune in to your emotional state of being quickly and perceptively. Psychic advice comes to me claircognizantly and clairsentiently through the strong connection I have with my spirit guides. I do sometimes receive specific words clairaudiently which I hope will resonate with you. I am a trained psychotherapeutic counsellor with a recognised diploma from a highly respected University College of Human Life Science. I chose not to pursue life science academically as I found it difficult to  block out  my psychic ability. So now here I am, ready to share my full rounded self, with my aim being to support people universally by providing clarity and insight in to their own life journeys. I was born in to a family that held strong traditional conservative values, and indeed one of my Grandmothers was a Methodist preacher at her local community church. I inherited my gifts from my other Grandmas side (Mothers Irish side), I heard rumours about my Great-grandmother attending seances back in the day, as at the time, such things were considered to be  Taboo . I guess I am telling you this to reassure you that I am aware of both the sceptical and believing side of spirituality and treat both with respect. When I am reading for others, I like to use Tarot as a tried and tested method of providing a solid foundation for any other psychic information to come forward. Spiritual energy has to connect through something and for me, Tarot is a reliable source, as well as your voice vibrations, aided by one or two crystals to amplify those vibrations. I consider myself to be a translator  between your world and mine. I will ask you to focus as deeply as you can upon the matter of concern and I find a context (work or emotional life), crucial to gain as much clarity as possible upon your query. We work as a team, with third party involvement!</Description>
    <Status>Available</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>4493</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>Yes</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4493-2</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge>
      <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4493-2_lf</Picture>
    </PicturesLarge>
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Clairvoyant</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairsentient</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairaudient</Skill>
        <Skill>Counsellor</Skill>
        <Skill>Psychic</Skill>
        <Skill>Channeler</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Tools">
        <Skill>Tarot Cards</Skill>
        <Skill>Crystals</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
        <Skill>Career/work</Skill>
        <Skill>Destiny/life path</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>None</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign>Scorpio</StarSign>
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
  <Reader>
    <Name>Elaine</Name>
    <Description>Elaine is a very experienced Clairvoyant who can explore details surrounding love issues in particular as well as help you understand whats going on with loved ones. Elaine will give you the confidence to finally move forward in your life.</Description>
    <Status>Available</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>4207</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>Yes</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4207-2</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge />
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Clairvoyant</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
        <Skill>Destiny/life path</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>None</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign />
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
  <Reader>
    <Name>Leonie</Name>
    <Description>I am a caring and experienced Clairvoyant Psychic and I discovered my gift from quite a young age. I was able to see and predict what was about to happen around them. I was able to help individuals on specific personal matters. I am here to guide you when you are feeling lifes challenges and will bring sunshine into your life. I specialise in love relationships and I am able to advise spiritually on career problems. I aim to empower and enlighten you, and my approach is honest and direct.</Description>
    <Status>Available</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>4468</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>Yes</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4468-1</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge>
      <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4468-1_lf</Picture>
    </PicturesLarge>
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Clairvoyant</Skill>
        <Skill>Counsellor</Skill>
        <Skill>Psychic</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Tools">
        <Skill>Tarot Cards</Skill>
        <Skill>Crystals</Skill>
        <Skill>Pendulum</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
        <Skill>Career/work</Skill>
        <Skill>Destiny/life path</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>None</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign>Leo</StarSign>
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
  <Reader>
    <Name>Sherrey</Name>
    <Description>Sherrey is an experienced Medium and clairvoyant. Sherrey will give you enough details about a loved one that you will instantly feel comforted and that you are speaking to a reader who truly cares and understands. Sherrey certainly doesnt give vague answers. She is a very warm woman that will tell you what she sees. It may not be what you want to hear but it will help you make the decision that is right for you.</Description>
    <Status>Available</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>4436</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>Yes</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4436-2</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge />
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Clairvoyant</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairsentient</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairaudient</Skill>
        <Skill>Medium</Skill>
        <Skill>Psychic</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
        <Skill>Career/work</Skill>
        <Skill>Pets/animals</Skill>
        <Skill>Destiny/life path</Skill>
        <Skill>Deceased loved ones</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>https://player.vimeo.com/video/881693496?h=5e7298981f</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign>Gemini</StarSign>
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
  <Reader>
    <Name>Margaret Ann</Name>
    <Description>Margaret has worked as a Psychic Medium for over 45 years. Margaret is compassionate and values her gifts a great deal. She will work hard to get to the the heart of the matter and bring you enlightenment. Margaret connects very well to Relationship matters, giving you the insight you need to make those all important decisions in love.</Description>
    <Status>Busy</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>4452</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>Yes</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/4452-1</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge />
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Medium</Skill>
        <Skill>Psychic</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>None</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign />
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
  <Reader>
    <Name>Caroline</Name>
    <Description>Caroline is a Psychic Medium,andclairvoyant  Naturally gifted healer, she is also an animal healer, and an empath. Caroline is also a Qualified NLP Master practitioner, Spiritual Practitioner, CBT Therapist,hypnotherapist, past life regression therapist, Reiki &amp; Seichem Master teacher has qualifications in herbalism and homeopathy. Soul &amp; Spirit Magazine 2013, 2014 and 2016. Caroline channels directly from spirit, receiving messages from her guides and clients guides or loved ones passed over.
Caroline was first aware of spirit in childhood. Caroline is the founder of Crystal Heart Psychics she has worked professionally as a psychic medium,&amp; life coach for the past 20 years. To pre arrange a psychic reading with Caroline, contact us via our e mail address or message us through our facebook page. Caroline ensures all of her psychic team are empathetic and caring in the most professional manner.

</Description>
    <Status>Logged Off</Status>
    <WebChatStatus>Logged Off</WebChatStatus>
    <WebCamStatus>Logged Off</WebCamStatus>
    <Pin>5330</Pin>
    <PinTier>0</PinTier>
    <OverFlow>No</OverFlow>
    <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/5330-5</Picture>
    <Pictures />
    <PicturesLarge>
      <Picture>http://services.inveroak.co.uk/readerimages/images/5330-5_lf</Picture>
    </PicturesLarge>
    <Audio>None</Audio>
    <Rota />
    <Categories>
      <Category name="Skills">
        <Skill>Clairvoyant</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairsentient</Skill>
        <Skill>Clairaudient</Skill>
        <Skill>Life Coach</Skill>
        <Skill>Medium</Skill>
        <Skill>Psychic</Skill>
        <Skill>Reiki Healer</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Tools">
        <Skill>Tarot Cards</Skill>
        <Skill>Crystals</Skill>
        <Skill>Pendulum</Skill>
        <Skill>Oracle Cards</Skill>
        <Skill>Angel Cards</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Subjects">
        <Skill>Love/relationships</Skill>
        <Skill>Career/work</Skill>
        <Skill>Pets/animals</Skill>
        <Skill>Destiny/life path</Skill>
        <Skill>Lost people/pets</Skill>
        <Skill>Past lives</Skill>
        <Skill>Deceased loved ones</Skill>
      </Category>
      <Category name="Languages">
        <Skill>English</Skill>
      </Category>
    </Categories>
    <Video>None</Video>
    <Rating>100</Rating>
    <StarSign />
    <emailreader>No</emailreader>
  </Reader>
</ReaderDetails>