<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<readers>
  <reader>
    <name>Elizabeth</name>
    <bio>I am an Intuitive Psychic and Life Coach and have been helping people for over 7 years. I use Numerology, Astrology, and Tarot Cards throughout my readings. I am here to help you have a clear image of what is ahead of you, how to understand and overcome situations and to show you the positive light that your journey has for you. I can focus on all areas of life, whether its love, relationships, family or work.</bio>
    <status>Available</status>
    <inveroak_id>4067</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Life Coach, Counsellor, Medium, Psychic, Astrology, Numerology, Tarot Cards, Crystals</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Deceased loved ones</areas>
    <language>English</language>
    <zodiac>Scorpio</zodiac>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Joanna</name>
    <bio>Joanna is a psychic clairvoyant. Joanna is a natural psychic, who was born with her ability. Joanna is also clairsentient which means she reads from the heart, and can feel peoples energies and emotions, whether they are in the same room or the other side of the world. This makes her insightful into what is going on in peoples lives, especially where matters of the heart are concerned.</bio>
    <status>Available</status>
    <inveroak_id>4456</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Clairsentient, Counsellor, Psychic, Tarot Cards, Oracle Cards</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Pets/animals, Destiny/life path</areas>
    <language>English</language>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Terry</name>
    <bio>Healing Mind, Body, Spirit & the Emotions. I have been successfully predicting the outcome of many client issues now for over 40yrs. I am a Clairaudient, Clairsentient, Clairvoyant a Spirit Guide Channeler, and can read into Soulmate, Kindred Spirit, Twin Flame Connections, plus interaction or communicational issues etc. Reading in an ethical, honest and integral way is part of my core, and my aim is not to give you false promises, but the way forward in love matters.</bio>
    <status>Available</status>
    <inveroak_id>4476</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Clairsentient, Clairaudient, Psychic, Wicca, Channeler, Tarot Cards, Crystals, Pendulum</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Destiny/life path</areas>
    <language>English</language>
    <zodiac>Aquarius</zodiac>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Tina</name>
    <bio>Tina is a Natural Psychic Clairvoyant who is also a very good Medium with around 35 years of experience. Tina can do distant healing helping you feel more yourself. Tina uses her guides and angels to help guide you and give you the answers that you are seeking regarding any situation you may be facing. Tina can also use the Pendulum, Tarot and Angel cards if requested, to give a very indepth and detailed reading. Tinas readings will leave you with a zest for life and feeling content with yourself.</bio>
    <status>Available</status>
    <inveroak_id>4375</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Medium, Psychic, Tarot Cards, Pendulum</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Destiny/life path, Deceased loved ones</areas>
    <language>English</language>
    <zodiac>Taurus</zodiac>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Ane</name>
    <bio>My approach to doing a phone reading is rooted in truth and honesty. Clients often find solace and clarity in my predictions and spiritual guidance. My psychic toolkit includes Clairvoyance, Clairsentience, Channelling, Soul Mate Readings, Spiritual Healing, Cord cutting with Archangel Michael, Crystal Healing, White Witchcraft, Spells and Rituals, Aura Cleansing, Angel Cards, Rune Cards, Tarot Cards, Light Worker. I hold a Bachelors degree in Botany from India, am a Reiki Practitioner, Spell caster, Akashic Record reader, Past life regression therapist, Angel healer, and expert in Switch Words.</bio>
    <status>Busy</status>
    <inveroak_id>4496</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Clairsentient, Clairaudient, Counsellor, Psychic, Reiki Healer, Wicca, Channeler, Runestones, Astrology, Numerology, Tarot Cards, Crystals, Pendulum, Oracle Cards, Angel Cards</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Pets/animals, Destiny/life path, Lost objects, Lost people/pets, Past lives, Deceased loved ones</areas>
    <language>English, Bengali, Hindi</language>
    <zodiac>Aquarius</zodiac>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Leonie</name>
    <bio>I am a caring and experienced Clairvoyant Psychic and I discovered my gift from quite a young age. I was able to see and predict what was about to happen around them. I was able to help individuals on specific personal matters. I am here to guide you when you are feeling lifes challenges and will bring sunshine into your life. I specialise in love relationships and I am able to advise spiritually on career problems. I aim to empower and enlighten you, and my approach is honest and direct.</bio>
    <status>Busy</status>
    <inveroak_id>4468</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Counsellor, Psychic, Tarot Cards, Crystals, Pendulum</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Destiny/life path</areas>
    <language>English</language>
    <zodiac>Leo</zodiac>
  </reader>
  <reader>
    <name>Caroline</name>
    <bio>Caroline is a Psychic Medium, clairvoyant and naturally gifted healer. She is also an animal healer, and an empath. Caroline is a Qualified NLP Master practitioner, Spiritual Practitioner, CBT Therapist, hypnotherapist, past life regression therapist, Reiki & Seichem Master teacher with qualifications in herbalism and homeopathy. Featured in Soul & Spirit Magazine 2013, 2014 and 2016. Caroline channels directly from spirit, receiving messages from her guides and clients guides or loved ones passed over. Caroline was first aware of spirit in childhood and is the founder of Crystal Heart Psychics. She has worked professionally as a psychic medium & life coach for the past 20 years.</bio>
    <status>Logged Off</status>
    <inveroak_id>5330</inveroak_id>
    <specialties>Clairvoyant, Clairsentient, Clairaudient, Life Coach, Medium, Psychic, Reiki Healer, Tarot Cards, Crystals, Pendulum, Oracle Cards, Angel Cards</specialties>
    <areas>Love/relationships, Career/work, Pets/animals, Destiny/life path, Lost people/pets, Past lives, Deceased loved ones</areas>
    <language>English</language>
  </reader>
</readers>
